We're on-site at the earlier 110 call.
Urgently requesting backup ASAP, over.
Excuse me, are you okay? Are you with me?
Oh.
Oh, I'm sorry. Were you sleeping, doctor?
Oh, good morning. How are you, Fuki?
I popped in to thank you for coming
with me to the vet the other day.
Oh, no, of course.
How's your cat been since?
Oh! Well, that one's been okay,
but of course, I've got another one.
And she's now in heat.
It's always something.
It's just hard for me to imagine,
getting propositioned at my age, you know?
Hm, I see what you mean.
But you know, there are men
whose libido stays perfectly intact
throughout their old age,
until they're on their deathbed.
If anything, sex drive…
So, now he's spending his mornings
chatting up old ladies and drinking tea?
Well, the story is
some grandpa she matched with
on a dating site for seniors
was trying to get in her pants.
Whoa!
Jeez, I guess even the older
generation is horned up these days.
At least this woman seems to have
an idea of what the hell we do here.
- Right?
- Hah! That's true.
Better than that old man coming in here
asking to have his dentures replaced.
Right. This place was
a dentist's office, so cut him some slack.
- Yeah, I guess, right.
- I think the lesson…
But there's always the chance
they know what they're doing
and it's all just an excuse to chat.
- Huh?
- Something as simple as cuddling.
Or holding hands
with someone who you care about
can increase that sense
of intimacy and security
that people are so desperate to feel.
SHIMOTORI
WE DID A FEATURE ON THIS PLACE.
I WANT TO CHECK IT OUT ON MY DAY OFF.
ARE YOU FREE?
This way, please. Yes, thank you.
The end of the line is right here.
KENSEIKITAN FES!
Perfect. It's this way. Thanks.
Man this oshikatsu thing is
popular, right? It's really crazy.
Bigger than gaming already.
Four trillion yen market.
And I heard 200 trillion worldwide.
It's more than
the national government budget.
God, I miss the simple days
when they'd just call us otaku.
- Wait, you're into that?
- All right, enough small talk.
Let's grab interviews
with the people over there.
You got it.
How do you guys find out about
events like the one we're here for today?
Oh, it's all through social media,
like X or even Instagram.
Gotcha. How did
the three of you first meet?
- We'd never met. It's our first time.
- We just met today.
- Your first time meeting in person?
- Exactly.
And what sort of oshikatsu
do you usually do?
Well, we basically travel and… Oh!
We take photos with
our acrylic stands and plushies.
Very nice, yes.
I can see you have a ton of merch.
How does that work?
Did you buy it with your allowance?
Yes, and some I got
as a present for good grades.
I see, so it gave you an incentive
to work a little harder?
What is it about them that pushes you?
Everything.
I just love them so much.
And when you love something,
you work for it.
You agree with me, right?
Yes, I agree.
So you blocked her on LINE?
Getting into a deep relationship
with someone
doesn't automatically
mean it'll end badly.
Even if you do end up
having sex with said someone.
It's repulsive,
just imagining myself having sex.
So instead of cultivating anything
meaningful with other people,
you're doing it with your patients?
I think finding someone, a close partner,
whoever they may be, is necessary for you.
Go out there and…
create a connection with someone
without running away.
And it can't be
one of your clients, either.
All right, I'm clocking out.
Sweet, have a good one.
Hey, you too.
Oh. Thank you for your hard work today.
Where do you go to buy your clothes?
Uh, secondhand places,
or I make them myself.
Like on a sewing machine?
No, a fridge. Yes, a machine.
Okay, I was just asking.
Oh, you can take off now too, by the way.
Cool, I'll bounce.
See you tomorrow, then.
I MADE DINNER!
I'M STARVING!
Oof, even when it's this
hot?
Hey, you okay?
Are you sick?
Uh… no, I'm okay, thanks.
I've just got a stomach bug or something.
SORRY, GO AHEAD AND EAT WITHOUT ME
Here, this is good for period cramps.
It's chamomile herbal tea.
Oh, y-yes, thank you.
So, you're Mio Inoue and you're 17?
She needs a guardian present.
I know. Her mom and I spoke on the phone
and I got her consent.
- She'll be here soon, okay?
- Mm.
So, last year was your first period?
Yeah.
That's late, isn't it?
It's usual.
Some girls get it earlier,
and there are those who get it
a bit later than others.
Actually, mine was also late.
Of course it had to come during gym class.
I was so embarrassed that I panicked.
No way! Are you serious?
The fact your cycle's been irregular
and you've been experiencing pain
preventing you from walking
is a little concerning to me.
We should consult with an OB-GYN
and continue monitoring you.
If any other problems come up, then
please don't be afraid to come in again.
Sex therapist? So…
Yeah, I specialize
in sexual therapy and troubles.
Eww.
Huh?
You can take this back, please.
I think sex is disgusting.
Oh!
Oh, but wait.
If you're an expert in sex and stuff…
Ooh. Then could you tell me how…
to have sex with these?
Fairy Café?
WATER FAIRY UNDINE
It's a type of themed café.
This one sounds like it has
the staff dressed like fairies
or something.
Might not be up your alley, Professor.
Yeah, no shot.
Apparently, she works there part-time
'cause she loves it,
and to make a few bucks.
Well, that makes sense.
She says, in order to be
more like her 2D anime character,
she needs to act
more like her 2D anime character.
So essentially, she's saying she
prefers a fictional 2D reality to her own?
You know, I hear that a lot
from young people in my lab.
Like, love isn't a good investment.
Whereas these fictional characters
won't hurt them.
Apparently, more young people every year
are holding ceremonies where they
legally marry their favourite characters.
Certificates and all.
Um… that's something
I'll never be able to understand.
And the only way you ever could,
would be to put yourself in their shoes.
Right?
Runerune firifiri moyamoya rin.
May I present your fairy dust?
I look like a freaking idiot.
We never judge patients
on their kinks and quirks, huh?
Huh?
No, no, look. I'm not judging them,
but this is insane…
Shh!
Koropokkuru,
fairies never raise their voices. Got it?
Got it.
- Koropo? Koro…
- Oh!
Welcome, little lost one!
- An apple is a fairy's favourite food.
- What?
I'll give you one if you do
that little dance for me again.
- What? No, I don't want to.
- Come on! Quick encore?
- No. Get the hell out!
- Please? Just one more!
- Welcome home, master.
- Sir, can I interest you in…
- Welcome!
- Hey, ma'am!
Can I please spend the whole day with you?
This is such bull!
They're even making me
mop the entire floor.
I know it sucks, But hey,
just look at the bright side.
You can keep
all the money you make over there.
Yeah, obviously!
But there's something off
about this place. It's shady.
What?
Well, some of the senior staff
are being asked out
on dates by the customers.
Here.
- And the store has no idea.
- Huh? Uh…
Well, I don't think
I'm working next Saturday.
- So yes.
- Great.
- Well done today, Koropokkuru.
- See you soon!
Thanks. Have a good one.
I spoke to the owner, and
you're gonna do a three-day trial shift.
Huh?
Three whole days?
Sounds like there's more
info to mine over there,
so you should stay put for the time being.
Wait? No way! Don't…
No!
- I can go drop this off…
- Yeah, it's on your desk.
- Probably need…
- Good morning!
- Morning, everyone.
- Morning! How are you?
- Sit down.
Mitarai, I had a look at your footage
from the convention. Good job.
- I appreciate it.
- This is good stuff.
According to a recent national survey,
nearly 20% of young people
have sexual or romantic feelings
for some kind of fictional character.
- Man, what a world we live in.
- Yeah.
How about this for a headline?
"Real love for the fictional."
- Ah.
- Right?
I think that'll
strike a chord with people.
- That's good.
- I think so.
It's good,
but rather than treating it so casually,
we could shed a light on
the more… negative aspects?
The idea of selling sex
or being sexually victimized?
I just worry that's a little too dark.
Sometimes the news should be upbeat.
It's good for everyone.
Upbeat?
It's all about getting numbers, right?
Besides this whole sexual angle
doesn't really fit your image.
- Right, Yumi?
- Right.
How about we have our cake and eat it too?
At the end of the story, Yumi can speak on
raising awareness for all this stuff?
Ah! That could work.
Well, if we're gonna comment,
we're gonna need to find something
that's a little more concrete.
Rather than just judging people, right?
We'd definitely need
something more concrete.
And either way,
I do think the "real love" angle
is the one people are
gonna be resonating with.
So make that the priority, all right?
- Good. I'm on it.
- Just keep it light.
- Will do.
- I want it ASAP.
- We'll get it to you.
- What's next?
CAN WE TALK FOR A BIT?
You told me whatever I wanna talk about,
you'd be here for me, remember that?
Here.
Aah.
I appreciate it.
I'm gonna do my best to tell that story.
Aah.
Thanks so much for having
my back with those guys.
It's a bit frustrating.
I admire you.
The way you speak your mind like that.
It's a real gift.
I should be more like that.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
I just tell myself
I'm too busy to have an opinion.
Though seeing you makes that difficult.
Feel like I should do more.
Hmm.
I know that feeling too.
Feel like you're constantly
being overshadowed.
I feel that with Miku.
You know, Miku does have
a lot of buzz around her these days.
But you know what?
I think you're the future.
The news is gonna need
people who tell the truth.
So don't give up, Yumi.
See ya.
Mm… There!
MICCHI
Now, let's see!
UNDINE
Oh, it's so cute! Look at that!
Wow, that's great.
Okay, I'll just give you that.
- Aw, thank you.
- Hmm!
- Oh, I get so nervous!
- Ready…
You got scared!
- You jumped!
- My God!
- You lose!
- Ugh, brutal!
You must save me, Hijiri…
Shukuchi!
KENSEIKITAN
You son of a--
Sorry, Kaya. I'm here now. Are you hurt?
Hijiri!
You know what this means,
don't you, Hijiri? You fool!
Laying a finger on the Shukutai means
going against the emperor emeritus!
So if you go through with this,
it is a betrayal against
the very god of this country!
If it means protecting her,
I'll cut down whoever's in my way!
Kaya, stay behind me. I give you m--
Oh!
Hi. Good evening.
Hey. Evening.
Wait, just…
Can I come in?
For sure. Yeah.
Thanks. Excuse me.
Mmm.
Whoa.
Did you do all this by yourself?
Oh, no, it's our office staff.
Mostly Marin.
I'm useless at that.
Got the plants from the previous
owner when he moved.
Marin loves them so much,
she'd swear it's the only reason
she hasn't quit yet.
Mmm.
Oh, uh… would you like to sit?
Sure.
Oh! That's hot.
Sorry to just pop in like this.
I couldn't get in touch with you,
and I was getting a bit concerned.
Basically, that's why I'm here.
Yeah, well…
it's just… been a little hectic.
Ow, that's hot!
So I should just believe that?
Huh?
I mean…
I thought you hated me.
Oh! Uh, uh…
That's not… No, no, no, no.
I don't. Not even close.
Well, that's good.
- So, are you interested?
- What?
In Kenseikitan.
Ah!
Um… I have a client who is,
so I've been studying it.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
It's popular.
Feels like everyone's talking about it.
Is she a fan of Hijiri?
Are you into it too?
No, we're just covering it.
Really?
Take a look.
This is a picture
from when Hijiri's super fans
bought out this massive electronic
billboard to wish him happy birthday.
That's so cool.
To be honest,
I'm a little jealous of them.
That you can be…
so blindly devoted to someone.
Even if they're not real people.
I guess I just wish
I could experience something like that.
Yeah, I was gonna ask,
have you ever had that?
I think that I've come close to it.
But I mean, if I don't know right away,
then probably not.
I get a certain amount of attention
because people see me on television.
That's usually a recipe for disaster.
I think they like the idea of me,
but after they get in bed with me,
they tend to run away, quickly.
That's the reason why
I'm kinda afraid of connection.
- You still take the train?
- Huh?
Even though you're a reporter?
Well, I'm not rich.
I don't make that much, dude.
Ah…
But what I do…
- Ah!
- There.
Hmm.
Tell me, what kind of clients
do you get at your office?
I'm sure it's a diverse group.
Erectile dysfunction?
Oh.
- Well, yeah, it's a pretty common thing.
- Hmm.
Over 18 million men experience
some form of it in Japan alone.
- If you include mild cases.
- No way! Actually?
Ah…
Do you get any female patients?
Mmm. Not a lot, though.
I'm glad.
Huh?
You know, that they have a safe space.
Women have a lot of intimacy issues.
And sexual desires.
Ah. Hmm.
Uh…
We can talk about yours if you want.
Oh, can we?
Might I remind you,
you left my messages on read?
I promise I won't ghost you
again. That wasn't cool.
I'm kidding, Ichito.
Women have sexual desires too.
Go out there and create a true connection
with someone without running away.
And it can't be
one of your clients, either.
YUMI ICHINOSE
UNBLOCK?
CANCEL / UNBLOCK
UNBLOCK
YOU HAVE UNBLOCKED YUMI ICHINOSE
Aah!
Aah.
- Yuta…
- Huh?
You ever gonna work
at your family's hospital?
What?
Not a chance.
No way.
I cut off my parents
and brother a long time ago.
Yeah, and now
your brother's running it, right?
Mm.
Even if I did wanna work there…
…there's no way in hell he'd let me.
Not that I ever would, though.
Yeah, fair enough.
- I'm happy about it.
- Huh?
I like Tokyo, you know?
And plus, it all worked out.
You transferring to dermatology
and everything.
Because, when you were in psychiatry,
it just looked like you were overwhelmed.
And…
it kinda felt like I became
secondary to a job you didn't like.
Oh!
Yeah.
Hmm.
No, it's great.
Sure, I work for someone
who's arguably certifiable,
and I've spent the last few days
serving coffee dressed as a fairy.
Yo, someone here is looking
for Koropokkuru right now!
What?
All right now, little one,
step back as I cast a spell
to make it even more delicious, here!
Runerune firifiri moyamoya rin!
Bingo! The deed is done!
You can drop the act.
This is the real me.
Why are you working here, man?
Hmm?
Why, what, sorry?
- Stay away from Mio, okay?
- Huh?
Mio! I don't want you anywhere near her!
That understood?
Hmm? Okay, I'm sorry, what?
Are you a fan of Undine?
If so, you should come when she's working.
She'll be here tonight…
Shut up!
You can stop with the charade, old man.
Old man?
Just so you know, fairies don't get old.
Ageless…
So you were being encouraged
by a male friend.
That's when your obsession first started?
We were in school together,
and we were both into anime.
Went to a bunch of events…
Then he said he wanted to come over.
Didn't seem weird,
plus I wanted him to see my collection.
Then all of a sudden…
…out of nowhere,
he went for a kiss and…
started touching my chest.
I told him to stop, and he said,
"If you really didn't want this,
you wouldn't have
invited me to your room."
Sometimes I wonder,
if I had just had sex with him,
maybe we'd still be friends now,
and it would all be fine.
I wonder that every single day.
So, that led
to your obsession with this guy…
Hijiri, no?
Aah. Yeah. That's the cool thing
about anime characters.
Even if there's no physical touch
in the relationship, you…
mmm, still feel connected.
Well, sometimes I wish it could
be like that with Hijiri.
But, I'm not an idiot.
Deep down, I know the truth.
I was a late…
you know, bloomer, so I guess…
Well, I guess that, um…
someday, I'll have to snap out of it
and step into the real world.
Or I'll never grow up.
- Well, that's not what I…
- Oh!
Crap! Gotta run! My shift.
- Here, I brought you this.
- What? Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Please don't let it go to waste.
- Okay.
- Oh, today's a big day.
- Micchi is coming.
- Micchi, who's that?
A customer who adores me.
So I should be going, because he's a fan.
It's nice, for once.
I'm the one with the fan.
Oh wow, I'm oversharing again.
I should really see myself out!
Thanks so much for your time.
Please enjoy that, okay?
I'm on my way!
- Here, for you.
- Hmm?
Hey, would you…
You're gonna see him outside the café?
Mmm. Yeah, but we're
just going to a Kenseikitan event.
- You said you didn't do dates outside.
- Be careful. Yeah.
Well, since it's Micchi,
I figured it's fine.
I mean, he is really into you.
- Just keep it strictly to the event.
- Mm.
Yeah, don't do drinks or karaoke after.
Just make sure you're careful.
Yeah, I know. Don't worry.
He is really good-looking,
though, isn't he?
- So it's not just me?
- No.
Isn't he a bit older than us?
Um, I'm pretty sure
he's in his fourth year of college.
- Ooh!
- So he's smart!
I'm taking off. Have a good one.
Oh, wait a minute.
Before, you mentioned
that you've made clothes, right?
Oh, uh, sure.
Do you think you could make
something like this?
Undine.
Or I guess I should call you Mio?
- Sorry I'm late.
- Mm-mm.
You ready to go?
Mmm! Back of the line's this way.
Wait a second.
I brought my car.
Thought maybe I'd give you a tour.
I'm good.
I don't like… driving.
What?
So you'd rather wait in a long line?
And in this heat?
Shukuchi!
You're staying here, Mio.
Uh… doctor?
Get lost! Trust me!
Why exactly are you taking
a minor for a drive?
Just so you know,
if it means protecting her…
I'll cut down anyone who stands in my way!
What the hell?
You people are nuts!
Hm. Why did you do that, doctor?
Oh, Yuta…
Um… Koropokkuru told me you were here.
That was scary.
I-I was terrified. Thank you.
It's okay, you're okay now.
I just got so caught up
in having my own fan for once--
You better never go near Mio
dressed like that again!
- Pathetic loser! You got that?
- Takeru! Takeru, stop! No!
He's a doctor from the clinic!
He was just trying to help me!
My bad.
I'm sure it looked weird.
Ah, ow, ow, ow, ow.
- Thank you so much again.
- Yeah.
I'm guessing you've been keeping
an eye on the Fairy Café?
- Hello!
- Welcome! Can I offer you…
The rumors I heard…
were that that place was known
for some, uh… really shady things.
So, just like Hijiri would,
you were just trying to protect
Mio from danger, huh?
Yeah, well, that didn't work.
Apparently, I just… made things worse.
I like… anime characters too,
but that doesn't mean
I don't like real girls.
It's complicated, I guess.
I thought that Mio understood.
I really thought she was into it
when she invited me to her home.
And that's why you said
those awful things? Because of that?
Yeah, but after that,
I started doing my research.
I learned a lot,
when it comes to sexual consent.
So you realized that just because
a girl invites you to her room,
that doesn't automatically mean that
she's consenting to have sex, yeah?
Yeah.
Mio…
I…
You need to know I'm really sorry.
Do you…
think we could be friends again, please?
Just know that you don't owe anyone
an answer at this moment.
I'm sorry I waited until now,
but why are you dressed like Hijiri,
doctor?
Oh!
I'm not gonna lie,
you kinda got me hooked on it.
I'm obsessed with him too, a little bit.
It's funny showing up here
dressed like him.
Gave me a little more courage,
you know what I mean?
Mm.
I guess…
the three of us are…
officially oshikatsu buddies, then?
Eh?
Maybe we should go check out inside.
We're already here, right?
Hurry, finish your drink!
Come on, you too!
Okay!
Here, I'll help you. Do you want syrup?
I know I don't need any.
Ooh, that's a good one! I'll send it.
KENSEIKITAN FES!
Hmm?
You're my first 3D fave, I guess.
Huh?
I'd like to thank you, doctor.
Doctor, move in a little.
Oh, yeah, sure.
You know, I should be thanking you too.
I learned about…
how love can look different to each of us.
Like, who's the patient
and who's the doctor?
Ready, then?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Even if it's not a physical relationship,
you can always…
still cultivate a connection.
So, thank you for my…
prescription, Dr. Mio.
Uh… you're welcome?
Man, that couldn't have been fun,
Koropokkuru.
I never wanna hear that again.
You know what's nuts, though?
We keep doing what the doc says.
Mm, yeah. Sometimes it's a bit much.
- It's just frustrating.
- Okay, give him a break.
No. It's me, not him.
I'm frustrated I always let him do it.
No matter what he asks me to do,
somehow I always end up doing it.
I even enjoy it a little sometimes.
Have you considered
maybe you like this, don't you?
Look, I know it's weird, but
I get why Professor Kurusu suggested it.
Oh my God, stop!
There's no way that I'm gonna be
a male nurse for the rest of my life.
Oh, sorry.
Yuta, Marin,
you're both good to go for the day.
Thanks. See ya tomorrow.
Everything! I just love them so much.
And when you love something,
you work for it.
You agree with me, right?
IS REAL LOVE FOR 2D CHARACTERS
DRIVING THE OSHIKATSU BOOM?
- Huh, is that a feature on Hijiri?
- Yes, I agree.
Getting more and more into it, huh?
- This event is extremely popular…
- Ah, yeah.
Who is the woman again
who's reporting that? Huh?
Yumi Ichinose?
Oh, right that's her.
God, she's pretty hot, isn't she?
I wouldn't kick her out of bed!
As I said, I think it's time
you both go home now, please?
Hold on. Am I nuts, doctor?
Didn't you get a call
from an Ichinose earlier?
- Huh?
- Oh, yeah. You're right.
Wishing you both good night.
- What?
- Huh?
Wait! Oh my God! Oh my God! Oh my God!
- Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
- No, no way, no way, no way, no way.
- Could it?
- Huh?
So? How is he?
You know I can't say anything,
due to doctor-patient confidentiality.
Are you really calling him a patient?
He's more like an experiment to you.
I think that's a pretty harsh way
to put it, don't you think?
Well…
I'll be keeping an eye
on this whole thing.
Hmm.
Ichito?
Yeah, it's… it's me. What's up?
You're the one who called, silly.
So…
Um, I was wondering…
if maybe you would wanna meet up again?
Even without
physical touch in the relationship,
you can still feel connected.
Maybe I should listen
to my own advice sometimes.
Seems to work on my patients.
- Hm.
- You know what?
I love how you say things like
"sexual consent." It's refreshing.
Mm.
Well, some people think that romance
is a bad return on investment.
Okay, but I think there's
much value in finding love.
- Whoa!
- Ah! Ah.
- Ah! Whoa. You okay?
- Sorry, sorry.
Jeez! It's really coming down.
My bad for saying
we should hit another bar.
No.
Wow, look at that. What a squall.
Ah. It's not really a squall.
Huh?
I wouldn't call it a squall.
To be really specific, a squall usually
involves heavy wind, not just rain.
Says the… former weather lady.
Oh, stop it.
Oh.
- Want this?
- Oh.
Thank you.
So, what should we do?
We'll catch a cold out here.
Oh, I guess, yeah.
I'll grab a taxi.
When you want something,
you work for it.
Ichito!
Forgive me.
I should've asked before.
Even with just kissing,
you need consent, right?
I just…
care about you a lot.
I did before…
and I never stopped.
Can I…
Can I?